("Runaway" by Kanye West)
♪ And I always find, yeah I
always find somethin' wrong ♪
♪ You been puttin' up wit' my
(censored) just way too long ♪
♪ I'm so gifted at findin'
what I don't like the most ♪
♪ So I think it's time
for us to have a toast ♪
♪ Let's have a toast for the douche bags ♪
♪ Let's have a toast for the (censored) ♪
♪ Let's have a toast for the scumbags ♪
♪ Every one of them that I know ♪
♪ Let's have a toast for the jerk offs ♪
♪ That'll never take work off ♪
♪ Baby, I got a plan ♪
♪ Run away fast as you can ♪
♪ She find pictures in my email ♪
♪ I sent this girl a picture of my hey ♪
♪ I don't know what it is with females ♪
♪ But I'm not too good at that hey ♪
♪ See, I could have me a good girl ♪
♪ And still be addicted
to them hood rats ♪
♪ And I just blame everything on you ♪
♪ At least you know
that's what I'm good at ♪
♪ And I always find ♪
♪ Yeah I always find ♪
♪ Yeah I always find somethin' wrong ♪
♪ You been puttin' up wit' my
(censored) just way too long ♪
♪ I'm so gifted at findin'
what I don't like the most ♪
♪ So I think it's time
for us to have a toast ♪
♪ Let's have a toast for the douche bags ♪
♪ Let's have a toast for the (censored) ♪
♪ Let's have a toast for the scumbags ♪
♪ Every one of them that I know ♪
♪ Let's have a toast for the jerk offs ♪
♪ That'll never take work off ♪
♪ Baby, I got a plan ♪
♪ Run away fast as you can ♪
♪ Runaway from me baby ♪
♪ Runaway ♪
♪ When it starts to get
crazy, then run away ♪
♪ Babe, I got a plan, run
away as fast as you can ♪
♪ Runaway from me baby ♪
♪ Runaway ♪
♪ When it starts to get crazy ♪
♪ Why cant she just runaway? ♪
♪ Baby I got a plan ♪
♪ Run away fast as you can ♪
♪ Twenty four seven, three sixty five ♪
♪ She stays on my mind ♪
♪ I-I-I-I did it ♪
♪ All right, all right, I admit it ♪
♪ Now pick your best move ♪
♪ You could leave or live wit' it ♪
♪ Ichabod Crane with that
mother-(censored) top off ♪
♪ Split and go where? ♪
♪ Back to wearin' knockoffs, ha ha ♪
♪ Knock it off, Neiman's, shop it off ♪
♪ Let's talk over mai tais,
waitress, top it off ♪
♪ (censored) like vultures wanna
fly in your Freddy loafers ♪
♪ You can't blame 'em they
ain't never seen Versace sofas ♪
♪ Every bag, every
blouse, every bracelet ♪
♪ Comes with a price tag, baby face it ♪
♪ You should leave if you
can't accept the basics ♪
♪ Plenty (censored) in the
baller-(censored) matrix ♪
♪ Invisibly set, the Rolex is faceless ♪
♪ I'm just young, rich, and tasteless ♪
♪ P ♪